[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following sleep disorders is more typical of a person with depression?", "correct_answer": "Late insomnia (difficulty staying asleep)", "incorrect_answers": ["Parasomnia (nightmares, sleepwalking, or other violent behaviors while sleeping)", "Early insomnia (difficulty getting to sleep)", "Sleep apnea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A joint NASA/ESA/ASI robotic spacecraft mission to Saturn and its moons was launched in 1997. What is the spacecraft known as?", "correct_answer": "Cassini\u2013Huygens", "incorrect_answers": ["Voyager 15", "Titan IV", "Ulysses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the CIA operation in which Bourne was involved in the film The Bourne Identity?", "correct_answer": "Treadstone", "incorrect_answers": ["Taylor", "Tyler", "Treadwell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what war is Steven Spielbergs 1998 movie Saving Private Ryan set?", "correct_answer": "Second World War", "incorrect_answers": ["First World War", "Vietnam War", "Korean War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the state motto of North Carolina?", "correct_answer": "To be rather than to seem", "incorrect_answers": ["Thus always to tyrants", "While I breathe, I hope", "By Valor and Arms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you serve absinthe, you pour it straight over a sugar cube, then add a small portion of water to the glass before tossing it down. After that, you should do this.", "correct_answer": "Light it up", "incorrect_answers": ["Pour into another glass", "Stir it", "Sip it"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What make of pistol did actor and Southern sympathizer John Wilkes Booth use to kill President Lincoln?", "correct_answer": "Derringer", "incorrect_answers": ["Smith and Wesson", "Winchester", "Colt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the hospital lawyer on Scrubs?", "correct_answer": "Ted Buckland", "incorrect_answers": ["Phoenix Wright", "Billy Flynn", "Lionel Huntz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This old large cat breed occurred naturally in Europe. It has waterproof thick fluffy fur and can survive very cold weather.", "correct_answer": "Norwegian Forest Cat", "incorrect_answers": ["Persian", "Squitten", "Ragamuffin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happened at the North Pole on August 3, 1958?", "correct_answer": "A submarine travelled underwater under the Pole.", "incorrect_answers": ["The northernmost US city, Naavetau, was founded.", "The first airport in the Arctic was built.", "The last Arctic Moa was killed."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nickname was Joe Clark given by the press in the movie Lean on Me?", "correct_answer": "Crazy Joe", "incorrect_answers": ["HNIC", "Batman", "Crazy Batman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Apricots contain carotenoids and antioxidants that may help to prevent heart disease.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]